<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ToIfe</string>
    <string name="new_user"><u>New User? Sign UP.</u></string>
    <string name="tilak_kamod">Tilak Kamod</string>
    <string name="user_name"><b>User Name</b></string>
    <string name="email_id"><b>Email ID</b></string>
    <string name="od_pass"><b>Old Password</b></string>
    <string name="nw_pass"><b>New Password</b></string>
    <string name="cf_pass"><b>Confirm Password</b></string>
    <string name="bio"><b>Bio</b></string>
    <string name="fhg">When you want to feel happy and energetic
    </string>
    <string name="combine_ora">
        Combine orange and yellow in your wardrobe. Not only will you feel more sunny, but you\u00E2\u0080\u0099ll project that image onto others, potentially helping to lift their mood.
    </string>
    <string name="when_you_ne">
        When you need to be calm
    </string>
    <string name="a_combinati">
        A combination of pastel green and blue colors work well in rooms where you want to relax after a stressful day at work, or somewhere within eyesight when you have to confront a stressful situation.
    </string>
    <string name="to_keep_you">
        To keep your spirits up
    </string>
    <string name="if_life_has">
        If life has been difficult lately, it may be time to bring in more yellow to your living and working spaces. Yellow is associated with optimism and good times.
    </string>
    <string name="when_you_re">
        When You\'re Tired and Just Don\'t Feel Like Doing Anything
    </string>
    <string name="get_some_re">
        Get some red on! This color creates energy and helps infuse your spirit with vitality. Rely on it to get you through a tough day.
    </string>
    <string name="when_you_wa">When you want some space to relax</string>
    <string name="get_some_gr">Get some green into the mix. Because of its connection to nature and the environment, it\u00E2\u0080\u0099s typically associated with relaxation and comfort.</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="book1">Becoming is the memoir of former First Lady of the United States Michelle Obama, published in 2018. Described by the author as a deeply personal experience, the book talks about her roots and how she found her voice, as well as her time in the White House, her public health campaign, and her role as a mother. </string>
    <string name="this_is_a_m">
    This is a memoir about a man who turned his life around after drug addition. Educational Themes: From the "ugly truths" of addition to believing in oneself, there is a lot to take away and discuss in Teaches how people in the worst situations can really turn their life around in The Fifth Vital.
    </string>
    <string name="a_redemptio">
    A redemption tale like no other: Behind the Mask is an unflinching autobiography from the British People\'s Champion that details - for the first time ever - the extraordinary story of the rise and fall and rise again of Tyson Fury
    </string>
    <string name="the_subtle_">
        The Subtle Art of Not Giving a Fuck: A Counterintuitive Approach to Living a Good Life is the second book by blogger and author Mark Manson. In it Manson argues that life\'s struggles give it meaning, and that the mindless positivity of typical self-help books is neither practical nor helpful
    </string>
    <string name="first_time_">
    First-time author and mental health advocate Shaheen Bhatt\u00E2\u0080\u0099s memoir is a very quick read. She effortlessly juxtaposes the puzzle of being born privileged and growing up with depression. This startlingly perspicacious book talks about the unpredictability of mental health in the most matter-of-fact way. Anyone who wants a moving personal account and an honest perspective on mental health can start with this gem.
    </string>
    <string name="ever_wonder">
        Ever wondered what your therapist is thinking during your appointments? If the answer is yes, go buy this book ASAP. Lori Gottlieb explores the world of therapy from a unique perspective\u00E2\u0080\u0094she writes about her role as both therapist and patient. You\u00E2\u0080\u0099ll find yourself gripped by the narratives she tells\u00E2\u0080\u0094some tragic, some hilarious\u00E2\u0080\u0094and in awe of the book\u00E2\u0080\u0099s astounding conclusion: We\u00E2\u0080\u0099re all human and flawed.
    </string>
    <string name="journalist_">
        Journalist Jenny Lawson\u00E2\u0080\u0099s memoir about her lifelong journey with depression and other mental health problems is equal parts funny and endearing. Furiously Happy explores the nuanced, often contradictory world of mental health, with a look at how people can thrive and find happiness in spite of mood disorders like depression.
    </string>
    <string name="the_quick_r">
        The quick read features the stories of 33 people who have dealt with mental illness in some form, with their commentary on why we don\u00E2\u0080\u0099t talk about it enough\u00E2\u0080\u0094and why that needs to change.
    </string>
    <string name="are_you_lik">
        Are you, like millions of Americans, caught in the happiness trap? Russ Harris explains that the way most of us go about trying to find happiness ends up making us miserable, driving the epidemics of stress, anxiety, and depression.
    </string>
    <string name="this_canoni">
        This canonical book explores bipolar disorder\u00E2\u0080\u0094a condition characterized by extreme mood swings\u00E2\u0080\u0094from the lens of someone who\u00E2\u0080\u0099s not only a clinical psychologist and expert on the topic, but also suffers from the disorder herself. Kay Redfield Jamison\u00E2\u0080\u0099s unique perspective on bipolar disorder as both the patient and the practitioner has made An Unquiet Mind one of the most well regarded pieces ever written on the topic
    </string>
    <string name="i_was_in_st">

    I was in std. IX when my dad was Transfered to Sambalpur. \u000D\n\u000D\nI had recently lost my best friend, one of the most trusted people of my life. I was in need of a support. Everything was new to me. And eventually, I made a huge blunder in choosing friends, probably the biggest mistake of my life. They misused my innocence and love what I had for them as persons and exposed me to addictions. Thankfully I wasn\'t taken into it. One of them became a very close friend of mine just to come close to and eventually  propose a girl who was my close friend. Again I was used. All of this distraction led my grades to detoriate. And all of a sudden I lost my maternal grandma, who was my very first inspiration. These heartbreaks and trust issues led me into Depression until a guy came to my rescue. He pushed me forward in every way he could. And helped me secure 92% in IX. But I didn\'t recover completely. I wasn\'t emotionally stable at all. Then another guy joined the school and unknowingly became very close. I was inspired by him. I saw a different perception of life. His personality was very like my grandma\'s. And without the knowledge of both me and himself, he made me emotionally strong and taught me self worth and confidence, which I lacked during that phase. These two guys played a huge role in my recovery and because of them I\'m alive. There were times when I thought of jumping off the terrace of our 8 storeyed building, cutting my veins,etc. But Everytime I was stopped by the visuals of my mom, my grandma, and them. The second guy insisted me to continue with my sports and music, which I had almost left during the phase ( I\'m a state level Badminton player and swimmer and I\'m classically trained in vocal and sitar). Yes indeed. Coming back into sports helped me a lot recovering. The key point to fight depression is to accept. Confidence automatically vanishes. But acceptance makes the task easier to get it back and right. -Neil Chakarborty
    </string>
    <string name="tug_of_war_">
        TUG OF WAR\u000D\n\u00E2\u0080\u009CWhy are you being so moody?\u00E2\u0080\u009D \u000D\n\u00E2\u0080\u009CWhy are you so quiet?\u00E2\u0080\u009D\u000D\n\u00E2\u0080\u009CSuddenly you seem more cheerful than usual.\u00E2\u0080\u009D \u000D\n\u00E2\u0080\u009CWhy are you such a cry baby?\u00E2\u0080\u009D\u000D\n\u00E2\u0080\u009CPeople like you should be put in a mental institution.\u00E2\u0080\u009D\u000D\n\u000D\nWondering who would say such hurtful things to another person? Well, \u00E2\u0080\u009Cabnormal\u00E2\u0080\u009D people have to hear these questions and statements on a daily basis from people who are \u00E2\u0080\u009Cnormal\u00E2\u0080\u009D. Mental illness is like a road trip that you never decided to take, and you are forced to drive without a GPS. Getting diagnosed with Bipolar Disorder was the beginning of one such road trip for me which started in 2016.\u000D\n\u000D\nI had always been a troubled child and found myself in a therapist\u00E2\u0080\u0099s cabin quite often. In one such visit to the therapist, after responding to a number of questionnaires, I was told that I have a mental illness, BD 2, and if I don\u00E2\u0080\u0099t start medication soon, my condition might degrade. I\u00E2\u0080\u0099ve been struggling with various emotional, physical, and social issues that come as a part and parcel of being mentally ill.\u000D\n\u000D\nPeople comment on my weight. My parents frequently worry that I might kill myself, who will marry me, will I have a normal life, how will people treat me when they come to know about my illness, etc. My close friends check on me regularly to see if I\u00E2\u0080\u0099ve taken my medicines or not.\u000D\n\u000D\nPeople who know about me having Bipolar say to me that I seem to be pretty normal. But well mental illness is not a physical wound that that can be seen externally. Have I recovered completely? No. But I have learned to manage my life and accepted Bipolar to be a part of it.\u000D\n\u000D\nAcceptance is the most difficult part of having a mental illness. It took me months to accept that I have a mental illness that cannot be cured. I started doubting myself, that how will I be a good psychologist when I am mentally ill myself. I even considered giving up on psychology because it felt like the subject failed me, studying it didn\u00E2\u0080\u0099t even help me take care of my own mind. I found it difficult to understand whether I\u00E2\u0080\u0099m doing something as a result of me being \u00E2\u0080\u009Ccrazy\u00E2\u0080\u009D, or because I really want to do that thing. There was a constant thrust I faced at every step in my life. There was anxiety about how people will treat me. There was fear because of the side effects of the medication. I was losing confidence as fast as I was gaining weight. I didn\u00E2\u0080\u0099t love or accept myself anymore. I couldn\u00E2\u0080\u0099t concentrate on classes because I used to be sleepy all the time. I was living away from my parents in a hostel, and loneliness was another issue that I had to deal with.\u000D\n\u000D\nIt isn\u00E2\u0080\u0099t as bad as it sounds. I am grateful that I have Bipolar. It helps me get a better insight into the lives of others who have mental illnesses, which in turn helps me help them. After four years, I\u00E2\u0080\u0099m stable, but there do come moments when the symptoms of my illness interfere with other aspects of my life. Regular consultation and sessions with my psychiatrist and psychologist help me stay stable and deal with relapse. Also, I have a very strong support system in the form of my parents, my best friend, and my dogs. I am grateful for them being a part of my life. I started working on spreading mental health awareness with my best friend, which acts as another anchor and gives me peace and stability.\u000D\n\u000D\nThere are some negatives and positives of everything that happens in life, we just need to find our light at the end of the tunnel. I dedicate this article to all those who had to take up this road trip. May you find your GPS soon.\u000D\n\u000D\n-Aishwarya\u000D\n
    </string>
    <string name="am_grateful">
        I am grateful to have finally embarked on the journey of healing.\u000D\nGrowing up, I led a life of privilege and security. I was sure that no harm could ever come to me till I had my heart broken. My boyfriend suddenly ghosted me and not knowing why pushed me in an abyss of depression. Life seemed miserable and I started harming myself and abusing prescribed drugs, which landed me in a rehab. My days in the rehab was horrible. I was physically abused and treated as a deviant. I thought I was going to die. Somehow I managed to escape and after a few months I left for London to pursue a masters degree. But the main reason I left the country was because I was scared that I would be taken back into the rehab again. I was traumatised and at my most vulnerable then and someone I trusted ended up sexually assaulting me. The rape completely broke me and I hated myself. I was ashamed and felt defiled. I often blamed myself for the assault and kept thinking I must have done something that resulted in the abuse. All I wanted was to just disappear from the face of the earth. There were days when getting out of bed seemed like a huge ordeal. However the support of my mother and some of my friends made a lot of difference. I also changed my psychiatrist and found someone who was kind, seemed to listen and understand. Medication along with therapy helped me to resume a semblance of normality. At least I wasn\u00E2\u0080\u0099t trying to kill myself every other day. \u000D\nIt\u00E2\u0080\u0099s been 8 years since I returned from London with a MA degree in Criminology. I\u00E2\u0080\u0099ve been working with survivors of human trafficking and sexual assault since then. \u000D\nI still have my bouts of depression and anxiety. There are days when I just want to lie in bed and cry my heart out. But on most days I feel thankful to be alive. It took me 10 years to let go of the hurt, pain and shame I was holding within me. I know that I still have a long way to go before I completely heal but I know I am progress every day.\u000D\n\u000D\n-Priyanka Biswas\u000D\n
    </string>
    <string name="being_a_dau">
        Being a daughter of a School van driver; I grew up in Mumbai chawl in a traditional middle-class family. I was told to choose an educational path because it gives the financial stability in our Indian culture. \u000D\nWhen I was 12th Std, I didn\'t get enough career guidance. When my board result got declared, there were inquiries about my careers from home. Initially, I was not studying for CET (Medical/ Engineering entrance) at all; because all I wanted to score good in 12th exam. Because of it I fell short andamp; scored less in the CET exam which I had given only for the namesake. I did not get admission for Med. / Engg. in any college on these marks. In this situation I dropped a year and I became clueless to the questions of my career that fell on me.\u000D\n\u000D\nMany of my classmates who got 50% marks were also studying in some or the other college. Having been at home for almost a year I went into depression, I had to hear from my relatives that a year has been wasted, then how will it happen next, will the wedding of a girl take place on time, etc.\u000D\n\u000D\nMeanwhile I met a friend who was doing Architecture in JJ School of Art. In fact, painting has been my favorite subject since childhood, but I never thought about making a career out of it. I always wanted to put a degree next to my name and after meeting her, I realized that architecture can be a career option. I believe, when we get options we are often confused. Due to our financial situation, we had no option/choice than getting admission in a government college. I prepared well for the exam and amp; got good marks too. In 2017, I got admission in the prestigious Rachna Sansad\u00E2\u0080\u0099s Academy of Architecture, Mumbai.  \u000D\nI could be the woman who has fear, who don\u00E2\u0080\u0099t have her opinions, who was quite andamp; shy inside, but I realize my potential to do, to be or to achieve anything that I want and wanted the world would see it. Today, I am not only an Architect; but a Miss India, Model, TEDX Speaker and but being independent and confident has always been my dream! Growing up and transform my life into a meaningful turn is what I learned from depression.\u000D\n-Pornima\u000D\n
    </string>

    <string name="for_me_it_s">
        For me it started with a fear I couldn\'t  recognize what  I am afraid of. I used to experiance it at around 8 o\'clock night it continued for 3 days.from the next day I had this for the whole day. I am an extrovert but suddenly I was not able to talk to anyone some thing was pulling me back.after that I stayed with my friend but nothing changed.i spoke to my mother about this ,then I took counselling\u000D\nI thought everything will become normal after that but the most scaring part came after that.i shut myself in my room as if I had nothing to thing about .sometimes I felt empty completely directionless!.then I started painting in my wall.some times I felt as if the pictures I drew frightened me.the only thing I understood was I need help I would scream loud for help.then I look medication slowly i unlocked myself from my room\u000D\nThose were the scariest days of my life I had suicidal thoughts. I could feel the burning inside me .after medication stage by stage I recovered and I got my new life of happiness.\u000D\n\u000D\n-Parvathy S. Pillai \u000D\n
    </string>

    <string name="at_21_i_rea">
        At 21, I realised that I had been in anxiety for more than 10 years, and considered that to be my "normal". Now at 26, I finally feel "normal", or to be honest, just like another unique human being. \u000D\nRealising that I had spent most of my childhood and all of my teens in anxiety, and then overcoming it, has now been a journey of five years. There was a time when I was anxious of seeing and being judged by my next-door neighbour too, but now even a laptop theft and the Covid-19 pandemic could not make me as anxious. \u000D\nAs a neurologically different person, hypersensitive, introverted, and probably dyspraxic too, I was taught that people like me are not successful in this world. This was a major bummer as I am fairly ambitious, have always been considered intelligent and sincere, and am keen to be a change-maker. \u000D\nThe journey of overcoming my anxiety has been a journey of recalibrating my beliefs, my entire being, and finding my passion for work and life. It has also been a process of forgiving my parents and closed ones, and realising that they are products of society too, and are probably just trying to do their best in looking out for me. \u000D\nFrom having zero self-confidence and dreading to wake up in the morning, I am now brimming with energy and faith, and am excited to wake up every morning. There are bad days, but I know they will pass. I believe in myself, and in my own power of creating my world as I want it to be. \u000D\nIf I can do it, you can do it too!\u000D\n \u000D\n-Deepika Srivastava\u000D\n
    </string>
    <string name="be_aware_be">
        Be aware\u000D\n\u000D\nBefore Sharing my story.I wanna say why I\'m sharing it.\u000D\nBecause of my extreme carelessness attitude, Till now I\'m suffering it shouldn\'t happen to any other person for people\'s knowledge to help someone who take it as chill!… Be aware of what you\'re going through.\u000D\n\u000D\n At the age of 15, I lost my father in that time,my thought was I\'m going through a sadness. I don\'t have any knowledge about what I\'m  going through slowly started losing my interest, I don\'t wanna eat and sleeping everytime was my best solutions.  In another corner. Being a single mother child, I have to scare leading  my daily life in our society. I wanna be in more conscious and be a protector of my family. People\'s around you don\'t know what your family is going through?.. I have to be more responsible.\u000D\n\u000D\nMy mom, didn\'t understood want I\'m going through whenever she saw me, I will be in sleep. After 8 to 10 hours  of sleep. I will be feeling tired. Still now!!…\u000D\n\u000D\nAfter getting my first job, Everything was going good.\u000D\nBut something started not feeling well. In that time, started facing jerks in sleep, severe headaches, unknown feelings inside my stomach. I can\'t able to get back to my normal, my thought leads to killing myself was a best option!!!!\u000D\n\u000D\nI was saying myself that, "Many reasons is there to die, but some hope is there live, love and laugh your life".\u000D\n\u000D\nAt the age of 21, I found out that I\'m in Depression, my mind refuse, to accept it, in that point. I was lackadaisical attitude, never take about it seriously. Even my mother don\'t have any knowledge that much about a mental health.\u000D\n\u000D\nEven I got rejected by a guy who I loved the most. No one will be there to help you and be with you to share, what going inside your mind.\u000D\n\u000D\nNow I\'m struggling alot, I\'m fighting myself daily to wake up. Everything because of my carelessness and I never took any steps forward to take care of mental illness.\u000D\n\u000D\n-Nadhini Muralidharan\u000D\n
    </string>

    <string name="you_don_t_h">
        You don\u00E2\u0080\u0099t have to be positive or feel happy all the time.\u000D\n YOU ARE HUMAN. Not a ROBOT.\u000D\nI\u00E2\u0080\u0099m a college student pursuing MBBS, since I never studied psychology, I had no clue why I felt that way. It started when I began feeling so unusual. I always felt that something was missing even though I had (and still do) great friends and a loving family. There was some unknown, unresolved issue inside, which I kept brushing off by calling it a normal \u00E2\u0080\u009Cmood swing\u00E2\u0080\u009D. \u000D\nIt was in November 2019 when I discovered I have been having issues with mental health. The feeling of suffocation within my body used to hurt so much. There was pain inside me, apparently for no reason. Some days it felt like living under piles and piles of dirt, and not knowing how to climb up and come out of it. I hated every bit of me. Every day at night, I wondered if this is who I am, a broken person, an empty soul, and if yes, then what\u00E2\u0080\u0099s the point. I couldn\u00E2\u0080\u0099t pretend to be okay anymore. I lost control of my body. I became helpless. I was frustrated each and every day.\u000D\nI knew I had to do something about my well-being, but the truth was reaching out for help was not an option, even my family didn\u00E2\u0080\u0099t believe I was struggling with my mental health. They thought that It\u00E2\u0080\u0099s all in my head and nothing to be worried about. They even told me not to discuss such condition with my other family members as they thought they would think of me as a weird and a crazy person who now needs a psychiatrist. I wanted to scream and tell someone that \u00E2\u0080\u009CNo, it\u00E2\u0080\u0099s not alright!\u00E2\u0080\u009D for a long time and to just save me from myself. I can\u00E2\u0080\u0099t believe I used to romanticize the idea of dying.\u000D\nEventually I had my \u00E2\u0080\u009CEnough is Enough\u00E2\u0080\u009D moment when I got completely frustrated with myself and it became too tiring to hate myself every single day. It was too much work. So one day I finally gathered my courage to speak to my father, about everything that I have been through. And then came the journey to seek help. I connected with a few therapists, had my counselling sessions and took antidepressants for the same. Yes, I was diagnosed with MDD [ Major Depressive Disorder] and that\u00E2\u0080\u0099s how my journey with mental health started.\u000D\n In this journey, my friends were my biggest support as they accepted me the way I was and didn\u00E2\u0080\u0099t tell me that I was being annoying (which I was). They reminded me that I am brave even on days when I barely got out of bed. The biggest lesson I\u00E2\u0080\u0099ve learnt along the way is that no one can understand how you\u00E2\u0080\u0099re feeling. Be with those who \u00E2\u0080\u009Cwant\u00E2\u0080\u009D to understand it.  I still struggle to get out of bed at times. Yes, it is tough. But I am tougher. When I was at my lowest, I used to think that this is who I am and this is my identity, but slowly I realized that this is only a part of who I am and not my whole identity. Having a mental health issue does not determine who you\u00E2\u0080\u0099re going to be. I\u00E2\u0080\u0099m not saying that I\u00E2\u0080\u0099ve overcome my darkest days and now everything is back to being great. I don\u00E2\u0080\u0099t like to sugarcoat things, so yes, there\u00E2\u0080\u0099s no fairy-tale ending to this. It comes and goes. But it does get better. I still have bad days, but now I\u00E2\u0080\u0099m more self-aware. I know what works for me and what doesn\u00E2\u0080\u0099t. \u000D\nIn the end I just want to say that please reach out for help even if it means talking about it anonymously online. You deserve help and you\u00E2\u0080\u0099re not weaker by asking for it.\u000D\nAnd to those who have friends struggling with certain issues, please don\u00E2\u0080\u0099t just tell them to reach out for help when in need, instead reach in and give them the love they\u00E2\u0080\u0099ve always deserved. Show them that you care and that they matter to you.\u000D\n \u000D\n- Neha Arsey\u000D\n
    </string>

    <string name="i_have_live">
        I have lived with schizoid anxiety since I was 13 years old. Every time I have a panic attack, I hear voices in my head telling me that nobody loves me, that I\'m worthless, that I should hurt myself or kill myself. Three times I have tried to follow through on their commands, attempting suicide that was (thankfully) unsuccessful. \u000D\n\u000D\nRecovering from a mental illness as part of the South Asian community has been a challenge. Due to cultural shame and stigma, I hid my diagnosis from everyone but my immediate family for all of high school. When I would have panic attacks at school or the temple, I would run to the bathroom and deal with it alone, when I really needed support from people. I also self-stigmatized a lot, thinking that I didn\'t need to go to therapy or take medicines, and that really hindered my ability to recover\u000D\n\u000D\nBut once I got to college I found my voice. I started owning my mental illness and taking care of myself, while also speaking about my experiences. Since then I have spoken to thousands of people about the importance of proper mental health care, and have followed my own advice and given myself the care that I deserve. I have not heard the voices for 2 years, and I hope to never have to hear them again.\u000D\n\u000D\n-Pooja Mehta\u000D\n
    </string>

    <string name="one_of_the_">
        One of the most important things I\u00E2\u0080\u0099ve learnt is that it\u00E2\u0080\u0099s important to speak up about mental health. Especially since I am a Psychologist. What I have learnt is that in the process of speaking up, its important to let people know that clinical depression, is something that I had and its okay.\u000D\nAnd that\u00E2\u0080\u0099s why; my mother rightly calls me a  \u00E2\u0080\u0098WARRIOR\u00E2\u0080\u0099 as I fight a battle where the scars are internal. A battle that most people don\u00E2\u0080\u0099t see as an illness but more as \u00E2\u0080\u0098feeling sad.\u00E2\u0080\u0099 What they don\u00E2\u0080\u0099t understand is that it\u00E2\u0080\u0099s a feeling of emptiness, a feeling of nothing, where you want to be \u00E2\u0080\u0098home\u00E2\u0080\u0099 even when you are. Because that home is the old you who doesn\u00E2\u0080\u0099t sleep all day and night and binge eat at odd hours and cries all the time. \u000D\nAccording to the WHO, India is the most depressed country in the world with the highest rates of depression and suicide. Despite this, there continues to be a sense of embarrassment and stigma attached to mental health and talking about it. People look down upon those who speak about it or experience it, in a way that is different from their outlook towards anything to do with physical health. \u000D\nFor those who experience any such thing or know anyone who does, don\u00E2\u0080\u0099t tell them that \u00E2\u0080\u0098its just a phase\u00E2\u0080\u0099 and \u00E2\u0080\u0098try to distract yourself.\u00E2\u0080\u0099 What you need to tell them is to \u00E2\u0080\u0098get help\u00E2\u0080\u0099. Talking to a counselor, a psychiatrist and building a strong support group is what they need. Talk about how you feel and what\u00E2\u0080\u0099s going on inside, don\u00E2\u0080\u0099t bottle things up until you want to explode one day. #DontBeAPressureCooker .  It is because of this learning and amazing support system that I have, that enabled me to continue fighting even when I didn\u00E2\u0080\u0099t feel like it. \u000D\nDepression is a battle that many people fight, what they need to be told is to not give up because life is a roller coaster ride where you aren\u00E2\u0080\u0099t in control of the speed or the curves and drops. There will be days where you will fall sick, lose some friends, get rejected for job applications but what it all comes down to is giving yourself time because you will be okay.  #NotAshamed\u000D\n\u000D\n- Kalyani Vaish\u000D\n
    </string>



</resources>